<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android" android:gravity="center" android:background="@color/themes_preview_background" android:padding="42dp" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content"  android:layout_marginBottom="32dp">
    <TextView android:textSize="24sp" android:textStyle="bold" android:textColor="@color/preview_text" android:id="@+id/font_preview_heading" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="Astronaut in The Ocean"/>
    <TextView android:textSize="12sp" android:textStyle="italic" android:textColor="@color/preview_text" android:id="@+id/font_preview_subheading" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:layout_marginTop="16dp" android:text="Chapter 1: Basic Theory" android:layout_below="@+id/font_preview_heading" android:textAllCaps="true"/>
    <TextView android:textSize="12sp" android:id="@+id/font_preview" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:layout_marginTop="8dp" android:text="The song “Astronaut in The Ocean” by the rapper known as Masked Wolf has as its first line “What you know about rollin’ down in the deep?” It is important that it is ‘the deep,’ not ‘a deep.’ Song lyrics, like poetry, are often metaphorical. As suggested by the song’s title, the central image here is of an astronaut in the ocean (commonly referred to as ‘the deep’), so metaphorically, someone who is used to soaring to the rare atmosphere, now plunged out of their depth. What is the depth is up for interpretation, but personal depression is certainly a valid interpretation. I would read ‘rolling’ as just a way of being or acting (as in “this is how I roll.”) By beginning “What you know…” is just a way of expressing the singer (persona) of being clueless of how to deal with being in this new and very strange environment, as if asking “Can anybody tell me how to deal with this?” The urban slang dictionary suggests “rolling in the deep” to mean emotional closeness and dependence, especially in a romantic relationship. A wolf is a predator. And a wolf in sheep’s clothing is putting across a false message (that of a gentle sheep) whereas their agenda is dangerous. Alternatively, the meaning could be more literal. The beginning lines sound like a person who has experienced nitrogen narcosis. Narcosis while diving (also known as nitrogen narcosis, inert gas narcosis, raptures of the deep, Martini effect) is a reversible alteration in consciousness that occurs while diving at depth. It is caused by the anesthetic effect of certain gases at high pressure. Then he changes direction to an analysis of his social relationships. Personally, I think the description of his narcosis has a certain flow and beauty with a touch of the danger of oncoming eternal sleep." android:layout_below="@+id/font_preview_subheading" android:lineSpacingExtra="1sp"/>
</RelativeLayout>
